3dcoat.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy – 3DCoat

At 3DCoat.com, we know you care about your personal information, so we have prepared this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to explain what personal data we collect from you, for what purpose and how we use it. It applies to the website [www.3dcoat.com](https://3dcoat.com/ "Opens internal link in current window") and all the services available through this website (together the “Service”) and other services of 3DCoat.com.

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of 3D COAT License Agreement and [Terms of Use](https://3dcoat.com/terms/ "Opens internal link in current window"). All definitions used in the Terms of Use shall have the same meaning in this Privacy Policy. 

By using or accessing the Service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

3DCoat.com may also collect anonymous information about people who visit the company’s main website, www.3dcoat.com, for marketing and advertisement purposes. For this we may use different tracking technologies also known as “cookies” of which you will be notified on the first access to our website. 

We collect the data you provide to us directly, such as when you create a 3DCoat.com account, use our Services or contact us for support. This data is used for the purposes it was given for:

  * \- Registration data (e-mail address and passwords, password hints, and similar security information used for authentication and account access) is used to provide you with the best experience using our Service and shall include collecting, storing and processing of this data by us and/or our partners (the list of which is contained in this Privacy Policy);
  * \- Other data you provide to our customer support (for example, first and last name, email address, postal address, phone number, and other similar contact data) is used by us to solve any issues you may experience when using our Services, for which we collect, store and process such data and, if necessary, transfer it for the same to our partners (the list of which is contained in this Privacy Policy);
  * \- Anonymous data which we get by recording how you interact with our Service or usage data from Service (this includes data about your device and the network you use to connect to our Service, including IP address). This data is collected for statistical purposes, which helps us to track errors and improve our Service. We collect, store and process such data and, if necessary, transfer it for the same purposes to third parties.
  * - We use Google Analytics service so we know how our marketing strategy and sales channels work. To find out more about it please read [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3123662?hl=en "Opens external link in new window")
  * - We use Facebook Pixel technology as well to make sure we reward our clients who found out about us from Facebook advertisement (more about it [here](https://www.facebook.com/business/learn/facebook-ads-pixel "Opens external link in new window")).

We use personal information such as your e-mail, date of birth, gender, country of residence and information derived from Cookies. Some of the legitimate purposes we profile personal information include:

  * \- to obtain a better understanding of what you would like to see from us and how we can continue to improve our Services for you;
  * \- to personalize the Service and offers you receive from us and recognise your loyalty and reward you with discounts and other offers, tailored especially for you; 
  * \- to share marketing material we believe may be of interest to you;
  * \- to help us operate our services more efficiently; 
  * \- to authenticate log-ins on our website and detect and prevent fraud.

We use the data as stated above on the following bases:

  * \- we need to use your data to perform a contract or take steps to enter into a contract with you, for example you want to purchase product or services through our website or you need additional information about them;
  * \- we need to use your data for our legitimate interest, for example we need to keep your email if you have downloaded our product for compliance purposes with licensing terms of such product, we also may use your data when we are allowed to do so under applicable legislation, for example, we may use your data for statistical purposes subject to anonymization of such data. 
  * \- we need to use your personal information to comply with a relevant legal or regulatory obligation that we have, for example, we need to keep your full details including financial data for compliance with tax legislation; 
  * \- we have your consent to using your personal information for a particular activity. For example, where you consent to us sharing with you special offers or newsletters about our products or services; and 
  * \- we need to use your personal information to protect your vital interests. For example, we may need to report about changes in our terms of use or privacy policy, or in any other case as required by law.

We will not retain data for longer than necessary to fulfil our contractual or legal obligations and to avert any possible liability claims.

3DCoat.com makes all the effort to protect the personal data of users. We use industry standard appropriate technical and organisational security measures, policies and procedures against unauthorized access or personal data disclosure. For example, the measures we take include:

  * \- placing confidentiality requirements on our staff members and service providers; 
  * \- destroying or permanently anonymising personal information if it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected; 
  * \- following security procedures in the storage and disclosure of your personal information to prevent unauthorised access to it; and
  * \- using secure communication channels such as SSL ("secure sockets layer") or TLS (“transport layer security”) for transmitting data that is sent to us. SSL and TLS are industry standard encryption protocols used to protect online transaction channels. 

To help ensure that these measures are effective in preventing unauthorized access to your private information, you should be aware of the security features available to you through your browser. You should use a security-enabled browser to submit your credit card information and other personal information at the Services. Please note that if you do not use a SSL-capable browser, you are at risk for having data intercepted. 

Should we experience or suspect any unauthorized access to your data we will notify you of the same as soon as practically possible but not later as applicable law requires us to do that. We will also notify of the same any government bodies which we are required to notify in cases stipulated by applicable law. 

3DCoat.com uses a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this privacy policy and periodically verifies that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible. We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information provided and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal Information

If you are habitually located in the European Union, you have the right to access, rectify, download or erase your information, as well as the right to restrict and object to certain processing of your information. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited circumstances. We describe these rights below:

 **Access and Porting**

You can access much of your information by logging into your account. If you require additional information, contact us at support@3dcoat.com. 

 **Rectify, Restrict, Limit, Delete**

You can also rectify, restrict, limit or delete much of your information by sending us the relevant request at support@3dcoat.com.

 **Object**

Where we process your information based on our legitimate interests explained above, or in the public interest, you can object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is needed for legal reasons.

 **Revoke consent**

Where you have previously provided your consent, such as to permit us to process your e-mail for receiving newsletters or promotional materials from us, you have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your information at any time. You can withdraw your consent by sending us the relevant request to support@3dcoat.com.

 **Complain**

Should you wish to raise a concern about our use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local supervisory authority.

If necessary, we will update this privacy statement, taking into account customer feedback and changes in our services. The date at the beginning of the document specifies when it was last updated. If the statement is significantly changed or the principles of the personal data use by 3DCoat.com is changed, we will seek to notify you in advance by e-mail or a general announcement on our resources.

The Service may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave the Service to read the privacy statements of other websites that collect personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by 3DCoat.com company via the Service.

Our website through which you obtain Services use cookies. A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences.

Unfortunately, we cannot provide our Services without using cookies. Please be advised that we use cookies as stated below. 

 **HOW DO WE USE COOKIES**

1\. To turn off the pop-up message that we use cookies on our website during your first visit.

2\. To track your action that you have agreed to the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy during your login via social networks or forum.

3\. To identify your session during your visit of our website.

4\. To determine your login at the website.

You may recall your consent to collect, store, process or transfer your personal data at any time by contacting our customer support. You may choose whether you recall your consent with respect to all the above or you choose to limit us in certain uses (for example, you do not want us to transfer your data to third parties), or you may choose to restrict us in using certain type of data you share with us. 

If you recall your consent to store data, we will delete it as soon as practically possible but not later than 1 month from the date we receive such request.

After your account is deleted we will retain statistical or anonymous data collected through the Service, including activity data, which may be used by 3DCoat.com and shared with third parties in any manner.

We share the personal data as listed herein on the terms as stated in this Privacy Policy with the following partners:

  *  **Bluesnap Inc.,** a California corporation having its address at 800 South Street, Suite 640, Waltham, MA 02453, USA, certain financial data such as name, surname, address and credit or debit card information for the purpose of finalizing payment for the Services.
  *  **SendPulse Inc.,** 19 Hill St Bernardsville NJ 07924 USA, e-mail address for the purpose of sending e-mails should you have agreed to receive them.

To understand more about our Privacy Policy, access your information, or ask questions about our privacy practices or issue a complaint, please contact us at: support@3dcoat.com.

We will provide you information regarding your personal data as soon as practically possible and free of charge but not later than 1 month from the date of your request to our customer support.

For the purpose of the GDPR _(Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation))_ the controller of personal data is Limited Liability Company “PILGWAY”, incorporated in Ukraine under No. 41158546, registered office 41, 54-A, Lomonosova street, 03022, Kyiv, Ukraine.
